# SUCHINLIN

User Experience Designer

% | 646-784-5590⊠ | suchinUX@gmail.comwww.suchinlin.com

### **ABOUT ME**

A bit about me and my "why" to designing:

I love helping people. Whether it's through projects or even something as simple as a passing greeting, I enjoy uplifting spirits and lightening loads. It's what brought me into nursing and now to user experience design.

Apart from design, I also am an avid runner and enjoy the discipline, expression, and community that comes with it.

### **SKILLS**

Design Tools

Figma

Sketch

Invision

Creativity

Procreate

Soft Skills

Empathy

Compassion

Creativity

Leadership

### **UX Skills**

- User Research
- Competitive Research
- Comparative Research
- Persona
- Sketching
- Storyboarding
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Interaction Design
- Usability Testing

## **EXPERIENCE**

NFT PROJECT

## Co-Founder and Designer

Sept 2021 to Present

- Hand-drew 230 total attributes for our 5-tier 10,000 piece collection
- Designed the UI, including interactions, for our custom marketplace
- Created website assets, promotional social media materials and content, as well as all instructional materials
- Managed and engaged with our 400+ member follower base

**POLLTAB** 

## **UX/UI** Designer

Feb 2021 to Aug 2021

- Conducted heuristic evaluation of client's website desktop and mobile and implemented 3 key UI design changes to improve users' flow by updating CTA buttons, imagery, and color-scheme
- Built foundations for updated style guide in brand's redesign

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO DESIGN

# **UX/UI** Designer

May 2020 to Present

- Collaborated with an engineer to launch 2 variations of my portfolio
- Developed and designed style guidelines (typography, color scheme, and components) and high fidelity prototypes on Figma
- Created personalized icons for portfolio use using Figma

MAKE AMERICA DINNER AGAIN

#### **UX Design Consultant**

April 2020

- Spearheaded team of 3 to better understand users' experiences and identify potential UX/UI friction points
- Conducted and synthesized research to guide design decisions 6 email interviews, 20 responses to custom-made survey, and 149 responses from client's existing survey
- Delineated users' experiences in a user journey map and pitched low-mid fidelity prototype addressing identified friction points

MOUNT SINAI BETH ISRAEL, 32-bed Cardiac Tele / Stroke Unit

## Registered Nurse, Unit Team Lead

Nov 2009 - July 2019

- Redesigned information boards and patient data collection forms
- Researched uptodate practices for policy and procedure committee
- Led team of 14 nurses and support staff through 12 hr day shifts

**EDUCATION** 

**General Assembly** 

UX Design Immersive

Jan - Apr 2020

**General Assembly** 

Visual Design Workshop

May 2020

**New York University** 

B.S. Nursing

Sept 2005 - May 2009

**Udemy** 

Drawing and Painting with Procreate May 2021